Rogério da Silva Yokomizo

Fullstack Developer, DevOps, with 8 years of experience. I have in-depth knowledge of PHP, Java, Python and Javascript languages, and solving complex queries using SQL. Solid understanding of the full web technology stack such as HTTP, DNS, cookies and assets loading. A very committed professional, who is interested in building scalable web apps in a startup environment, focusing on results. Currently I work at Rocket Internet with experience in team management, code review, cost optimization, service integration and on-call time.

Experience

Rocket Internet Jun 2012 - Present

Rocket Internet is a venture capital focused on online and mobile retail services. There I have worked on different projects such as:

- Vaniday (Jul 2015 Present)
- RideLink (Mar 2015 Jun 2015)
- Airu (Jun 2012 Feb 2015)

After more than four years, I have experienced:

- Team management
- Hiring and coaching process
- Building projects from scratch
- Cost optimization
- On-call time
- Infrastructure / Operation

The main technologies I have used are C#, Java, PHP, Javascript, ES6, CSS, AngularJS, JQuery, Sass, Less, Docker, DynamoDB, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Spring, Playframework, Stripes and Symfony.

Projeto Fígado May 2014 - Jun 2014

Projeto Fígado is a platform to improve the liver transplantation in São Paulo. It was developed inside the Faculdade de Tecnologia do Estado de São Paulo and Secretaria da Saúde do Estado de São Paulo. I built a mobile app using Phonegap and AngularJS.

Atados Dec 2012 - Sep 2013

Atados is a social network that matches volunteers with nonprofits. I worked as Python Developer using Django Framework.

Catho Dec 2010 - May 2012

Catho is a job site where I worked to maintaining the resume and CRM platforms, using PHP, MySQL, Solr, Smarty, Javascript and JQuery.

Jovem Pan Aug 2009 - Nov 2010

Jovem Pan is a Brazilian radio network. I worked with PHP, MySQL, Javascript, JQuery and CSS.

Wheaton Brasil Aug 2008 - Jul 2009

Wheaton Brasil is a Brazilian glass manufacturer, where I worked to integrate its systems with Oracle e-business suite (EBS). I worked with PHP, Oracle SGBD, Oracle Reports, PostgreSQL, Smarty, Javascript and CSS.

Education

Faculdade de Tecnologia do Estado de São Paulo - Tecnologia em Informática para Gestão de Negócios

Languages

- English
- Portuguese

_

Rogério da Silva Yokomizo <me@ro.ger.io>
26 years old, Brazilian, Bluecard
Berlin - Germany
Get the latest version of this document at http://ro.ger.io/resume.html